{
    "subject": "resource/Nicholas_Brown,_Jr.",
    "predicate": "ontology/residence",
    "object": "resource/Providence,_Rhode_Island",
    "human_readable": "Nicholas Brown Jr.'s residence is Providence, Rhode Island.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9792006015777588,
            "question": "Is Nicholas Brown Jr. living in Rhode Island?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8964739441871643,
            "question": "What state is Nicholas Brown Jr.'s residence in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8282750844955444,
            "question": "Where does Nicholas Brown Jr. reside?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7704818248748779,
            "question": "Can you tell me the location of Nicholas Brown Jr.'s residence?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.743087112903595,
            "question": "In which city is Nicholas Brown Jr.'s home located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7067820429801941,
            "question": "Providence is the home of who?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6811198592185974,
            "question": "What is the name of the place where Nicholas Brown Jr. resides?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6785929203033447,
            "question": "Where does Nicholas Brown Jr. live?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6341041922569275,
            "question": "I'm looking for the city where Nicholas Brown Jr. lives."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44649121165275574,
            "question": "What is the address of Nicholas Brown Jr.?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Nicholas Brown Jr.'s residence is Providence, Rhode Island.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2846_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=I'm looking for the city where Nicholas Brown Jr. lives.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2846_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where does Nicholas Brown Jr. live?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2846_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the place where Nicholas Brown Jr. resides?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2846_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2846_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2846_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2846_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2846_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2846_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2846_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2846_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2846_91.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2846_95.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2846_97.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provided contain information about various Nicholas Browns, including one who was born in Providence and had connections to Portsmouth, Rhode Island. While the specific details do not directly state that Nicholas Brown Jr.'s residence is Providence, Rhode Island, the context of his birth and early life in Providence, along with his association with the city through the founding of Brown University, strongly supports this conclusion. Therefore, based on the given information, the statement can be considered correct."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}